(忆往昔)
怎么样  我们一起去杀些凶鬼恶灵
So, what do you say we kill some evil sons of bitches.
惹点麻烦吧
And we raise a little hell?
萨姆  小心
Sam. Look out.
萨姆
Sam.
你要拿自己的灵魂换吗
You're offering up your own soul?
你只需要复活萨姆
All you gotta do is bring Sam back.
我给你一年  就一年
I'll give you one year and one year only.
我不能让他死  鲍比
I couldn't let him die, Bobby.
他是我弟弟
He's my brother.
我真想掐死你
I could throttle you.
不管我需要做什么  我一定要帮你脱困
I don't care what it takes. I'm gonna get you out of this.
如果我们困住一个十字路口恶魔
We trapped a Crossroads demon.
想办法钻交易的空子
Try to welch our way out of the deal in any way,
你就会死
you die.
什么样的刀能杀恶魔
What kind of blade can kill a demon?
昨天的话  我会说没有这种东西
Yesterday, I'd have said there was no such thing.
那无名小妞是谁
Who was that masked chick?
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
我是刚救了你的姑娘
I'm the girl that just saved your ass.
(如今)
(印第安纳州  西塞罗)
亲爱的
Sweetie.
谢谢你送她回来
Thanks for driving her back here.
我又没有选择
Well, it's not like I had a choice.
她大发脾气
She pitched a fit.
亲爱的
Sweetie.
怎么了
What's wrong?
没事
Nothing.
我想你了
I missed you.
但今晚你该去爸爸家住
Okay, but tonight's Dad's night.
不
No.
我不喜欢去爸爸家住
I don't like Dad's night.
我再不想去爸爸家住了
I don't want Dad to have a night anymore.
怎么突然这么说
Since when?
你以前明明喜欢去爸爸家住
You used to love going to your dad's house.
他爱你
You know, he loves you.
而且也很想你
And he misses you a lot.
但我讨厌那里
But I hate it there.
- 你不讨厌那里  - 我就是讨厌
- You don't hate it. - Yes, I do.
他好凶  那里还有怪物
He's mean. And there are monsters there.
我再不想去了
I don't want to go back.
求你别让怪物抓到我
Please don't let the monsters get me.
好吧  亲爱的
Okay, sweetie.
好
Okay.
[邪恶力量 第3季第2集]
什么叫你不觉得会成功  鲍比
What do you mean you don't think it'll work, Bobby?
那不是恶魔驱逐仪式吗
It's a demon-dispelling ritual.
或许我们翻译错了
Well, maybe we got the translation wrong.
我们不能就任由迪恩在地狱里煎熬
Look, we can't let Dean fry in hell while we...
(翻译文件)
肯定有什么能...
Well, there's gotta be something that will...
好吧  不不
Okay, yeah. No. No.
我得挂了  不说了
I gotta go. All right.
那是谁
Who was that?
我就是在叫披萨
I was just ordering pizza.
哥们  你知道你就在餐馆里吧
Dude, you do realize that you're in a restaurant?
嗯  是的
Yeah. Yeah, oh, yeah. I
我就是好想吃披萨
just felt like pizza, you know?
好吧  古怪小子
Okay, Weirdy McWeirderton.
我可能有发现
So I think I got something.
是吗
Yeah?
印第安纳州西塞罗
Cicero, Indiana.
有个男人跌在了自己的电锯上
Falls on his own power saw.
(男子在家中因事故惨死)
还有呢
And?
怎么  就这吗
What, that's it?
一个电锯
One power saw?
是的
Well, yeah.
你觉得这是案子吗
And you think that this is a case?
我不知道  可能吧
Well, I don't know. Could be.
我不知道  迪恩
I don't know, Dean, I...
好吧  西塞罗还有比
All right. There's something better in...
案子更好的东西
Better in Cicero than just a case.
是什么
And that is?
莉莎·布雷登
Lisa Braeden.
我该问吗
Should I even ask?
记得我去公路旅行过一次吗
Remember that road trip I took...
大概八年前了
about eight years ago?
你当时和爸爸在奥兰多
Now, you were in Orlando with Dad...
- 了结那个死亡女妖的案子  - 嗯
- wrapping up that Banshee thing. - Yeah, yeah. The...
- 五天五州  - 对
- Five States, five days. - Yeah.
- 是啊  - 对
- Well, - Right.
算是吧
kind of.
但我大部分时间其实是在莉莎·布雷登家度过的
Although, I spent most of my time in Lisa Braeden's loft.
是这么回事吗
So let me get this straight.
你要一路开去西塞罗
You wanna drive all the way to Cicero
跟个小妞鬼混
just to hook up with some random chick?
她是个瑜伽老师
She was a yoga teacher.
那是我这辈子最柔软的周末
That was the bendiest weekend of my life.
拜托  行行好吧
Come on, have a heart, huh?
这是我的临终遗愿
It's my dying wish.
你还有多少临终遗愿啊
Yeah. Well, how many dying wishes are you gonna get?
能有多少是多少
As many as I can squeeze out.
拜托
Come on.
笑一个  萨姆
Smile, Sam.
天知道我跟冈比度过24小时后肯定笑得合不拢嘴
God knows I'm gonna be smiling after 24 hours with Gumby girl.
冈比
Gumby girl.
那我是她身边的红马波奇吗
Does that make me Pokey?
(西塞罗松林汽车旅馆  有空房)
不用等我了  萨姆
Don't wait up for me, Sammy.
迪恩
Dean, Dean...
(晨山小区  售罄)
迪恩
Dean.
莉莎
Lisa.
你好吗
How's it going?
多久没见了
So how long's it been?
八年了  要九年了
Eight, going on nine years now.
真疯狂  是吧
Crazy, right?
是啊
Yeah.
你怎么来这里了
So, what are you doing here?
我正好经过
I was just... I was passing through, and I
实在没忍住
couldn't resist.
我记得你喜欢惊喜
I remembered that you love surprises.
嗯
Yeah.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester.
简直了
Just wow.
抱歉  你来得不太巧
I'm sorry. You kind of came at a bad time.
我们在办派对
We're having a party.
派对
Party?
我喜欢派对
Well, I love parties.
这是谁的派对
So who's the party for?
本  我儿子
Ben. My son.
- 你有...  - 是的
- You have a...? - Yeah.
那就是他
That's him.
太好了  AC/DC最酷了
Yes! AC/DC rules!
太棒了
Awesome.
- 太酷了  - 他多大...
- That is so cool. - How old...?
八岁
Eight.
迪恩  可以失陪一下吗
Dean, could you excuse me a minute?
嗯  当然  别担心我
Yeah, sure, don't mind me.
你听到莉莎喊他迪恩了吗
Did you hear Lisa call him Dean?
嗯  怎么了
Yeah, why?
你不知道迪恩吗
You don't know about Dean?
那个迪恩  我这辈子最美妙的一夜的迪恩
The Dean? Best-Night-of-My-Life Dean?
不知道  跟我说说
No. Tell me.
天啊
My God.
他们共度了疯狂  几乎不合法的...
So they had this crazy, semi-illegal...
你好
Hello.
你好啊
What's up?
你好吗
What's up with you?
今天是你生日
So it's your birthday.
没错
Guilty.
派对挺不错
It's a cool party.
哥们  这简直太棒了
Dude, it's so freaking sweet.
还有这个蹦床  简直牛叉
And this Moonbounce? It's epic.
是啊  是很棒
Yeah, it's pretty awesome.
你知道还有谁觉得它很棒吗
You know who else thinks they're awesome?
小妞
Chicks.
那简直像座辣妹之城
It's like hot-chick city out there.
小心  女士们  麻烦来了
Look out, ladies, here comes trouble.
你还好吗
So how you holding up?
挺好
Fine.
真的吗
Really?
嗯  还好吧
Yeah, you know.
我...
I just...
算了
Never mind.
怎么了
What?
就是...
It's just...
我担心凯蒂
I'm worried about Katie.
我觉得她可能
I think there might be something...
有点问题
wrong with her.
当然了
Of course there is.
小可怜刚失去了爸爸  她肯定难过死了
Poor girl just lost her dad, she's devastated.
不  我不是那意思
No, that's not what I'm talking about.
她真的有很大的问题
There is something really wrong with her.
我不确定凯蒂
I'm not sure that Katie is...
是凯蒂
Katie.
什么
What?
我不确定那是我女儿
I'm not sure that's my daughter.
我知道你很悲痛
I know you're grieving.
但你不能说这种话  凯蒂需要你
But you can't talk like that. Katie needs you now.
- 不  你不懂  - 说真的
- No. You don't understand... - Seriously.
我们会找人帮你
We're gonna get you help.
你会没事的
It'll be okay.
凯蒂
Katie.
来吧  我们走
Come on, we're leaving.
我见过本了
So I met Ben.
这孩子不错
Cool kid.
嗯
Yeah.
我不禁注意到
You know, I couldn't help but notice that
他要八岁了
he's turning 8.
你和我  那个...
You and me. You know.
你是想问他是不是你的吗
You're not trying to ask me if he's yours?
不  当然不是
No, no, of course not.
他不是吧
He's not, is he?
什么
What?
不是
No.
好吧
Right.
嗯
Yeah.
凯蒂  亲爱的  我们得走了  好吗  来
Katie, sweetheart, we gotta go, okay? Come on.
来吧  凯蒂
Come on, Katie.
你朋友出什么事了吗
Something wrong with your friend?
她经历了很多事
She's been through a lot.
她前夫刚因一起可怕的事故而死
Her ex just died in this horrible accident.
嗯  我读到了
Yeah. Didn't I just read about that?
- 电锯吧  - 对
- The power saw? - Yeah.
近来这一带真是
I guess there's been a lot of bad luck
厄运连连
in the neighborhood lately.
什么意思
What kind of bad luck?
(西塞罗松林汽车旅馆  有空房)
你好  萨姆
Hello, Sam.
你从林肯之后就一直在跟踪我
You've been following me since Lincoln.
你还真是洞若观火
Not much gets by you, huh?
这个太好吃了
These are amazing.
简直像油炸可卡因  尝尝
It's like deep-fried crack. Try some.
你的那把刀
That knife you had...
你能拿它杀恶魔吗
you can kill demons with that thing?
我需要从天而降拯救落难少女时
Sure comes in handy when I have to swoop in
的确非常方便
and save the damsel in distress.
- 你从哪弄来的  - 超市
- Where'd you get it? - SkyMall.
你为什么跟踪我
Why are you following me?
我对你有兴趣
I'm interested in you.
为什么
Why?
因为你高
Because you're tall.
我喜欢高个男人
I love a tall man.
还有反基督什么的
And then there's the whole antichrist thing.
- 什么  - 你懂的
- Excuse me? - You know,
一代灵力者孩子
generation of psychic kids.
黄眼恶魔把你们集结起来
Yellow-Eyed Demon rounds you up,
然后是《名人大乱斗》
Celebrity Deathmatch ensues...
你是唯一幸存者
you're the sole survivor.
这你怎么知道的
How do you know about that?
我是个好猎人
I'm a good hunter.
黄眼恶魔曾经对你有大计划啊  萨姆
So Yellow Eyes had some prettty big plans for you, Sam.
曾经是关键词
Had being the key word.
对对  没错
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's right.
叮咚  恶魔死了
Ding-dong, the demon's dead.
干得漂亮
Good job with that.
但你仍然很特别
It doesn't change the fact that you're special.
像《死亡地带》里的安东尼·迈克尔·豪尔一样
In that Anthony-Michael-Hall,
- 有超感幻象的能力  - 不
- ESP-vision kind of way. - No.
不  那已经停止了
No, that stuff's not happening anymore.
自黄眼恶魔死后就停止了
Not since Yellow Eyes died.
我觉得你还是个重要人物
I'm thinking you're still a big deal.
考虑到你妈妈的那些事
I mean, after all that business with your mom.
我妈妈怎么了
What about my mom?
就是她朋友们的遭遇
You know, what happened to her friends.
你不知道吗
You don't know.
你需要好好了解些情况了  朋友
You've got a little bit of catching up to do, my friend.
你去查查你妈妈的朋友们吧
So why don't you look into your mom's pals...
然后给我打电话
and then give me a call
我们到时再聊
and we'll talk again.
对了  你知道镇上有件案子吧
And by the way, you do know there's a job in this town, right?
- 喂  - 哥们
- Hello? - Dude.
这里真有案子
There is a job here.
是吗
Really?
嗯  记得我们在报上看到的
Yeah. You know that one freak accident
那一起意外事故吗
we read about in the paper?
原来还有四起  根本都没登报
Turns out there's four more that never even made the paper.
都发生在这间晨山封闭小区里
All in this Morning Hill gated community.
有人从梯子上摔下
People falling off ladders,
还有淹死在热浴盆里的  小区里到处死人
drown in Jacuzzis all over the neighborhood.
这是很奇怪
That is weird.
是啊  绝对有问题
Yeah. Something's up.
漂亮的小区大门也挡不住的问题
Something these nice big gates can't protect them from.
凯蒂
Katie.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
跟我玩吧  妈妈
Play with me, Mommy.
好啊  好  我们玩吧
Okay, sure. Yeah, let's... let's play.
好
Good.
我爱你  妈妈
I love you, Mommy.
我也爱你  亲爱的
I love you too, sweetie.
我饿了  妈妈
I'm hungry, Mommy.
嗯
Yeah.
我再次为打扰您表示道歉
So once again, I'm very sorry to disturb you.
我们只想尽快兑现人寿保险
We just wanna really expedite that life-insurance policy.
- 当然  - 好
- Of course. - Okay.
这就是他摔下来的地方
This is where he fell.
这样啊
I see.
他究竟是怎么...
Now, how exactly did he...?
他就在屋里  换灯泡
He was just inside, changing a light bulb.
肯定是没站稳
Must've lost his balance.
- 事发时你在场吗  - 不
- Were you here when this happened? - No.
我当时出去了
I was out.
只有我们女儿达科塔在
The only one here was our daughter, Dakota.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  我想我该问的都问了
Okay, well, I think that's all I need.
- 好  - 那我不打扰你了
- Okay. - I'll get out of your way now.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢  妈妈
Thank you, Mommy.
你吃吧
You eat.
妈妈就回来
Mommy will be right back.
妈妈
Mommy?
给妈妈点时间
Just... Just give Mommy a second.
让我进去
Let me in.
妈妈
Mommy?
让我进去
Let me in.
妈妈
Mommy.
让我进去
Let me in!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
- 给妈妈点时间  - 让我进去
- Just give Mommy a minute. - Let me in!
让我进去
Let me in,
let me in!
让我进去
Let me in!
给妈妈点时间
Just give Mommy a minute.
你真是太可爱了
Aren't you just the cutest thing.
谢谢
Thank you.
凯蒂  可以把这个放进厨房吗  拜托
Katie, could you put these in the kitchen, please.
- 凯蒂似乎还好  毕竟...  - 她没事
- Katie seems okay considering... - She's fine. Yeah.
- 听着  - 你呢
- Look... - And you?
你还好吗  说真的
How are you doing, really?
我很好
I'm fine.
我们都好  现在真的不方便
Look, we're fine. And this isn't a good time...
我就是不知道你是打算留着房子
I just wasn't sure if you're planning on keeping the house...
还是出售  我们西塞罗地产
or selling. We at Cicero Realty...
我说了  现在不方便
Look, I told you it's not a good time.
我要吃冰淇淋
I want ice cream.
妈妈  冰淇淋  好吗
Mommy. Ice cream, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
伙计们
Guys.
捉迷藏
Hide-and-seek, hide-and-seek.
本
Ben.
你去过我的派对
You were at my party.
对
Yeah.
我是迪恩
Yeah, I'm Dean.
你还好吗  出什么事了吗
Everything okay? Something wrong?
他们玩的是你的游戏机吗
That your game they're playing with?
瑞恩·翰弗莱借走了
Ryan Humphrey borrowed it.
现在他不肯还了
And now he won't give it back.
- 要我去...  - 不
- Well, you want me to go...? - Don't.
别去
Don't go over there.
只有小贱人才找大人
Only bitches send a grownup.
你没说错
You're not wrong.
我也不是小贱人
And I am not a bitch.
那是翰弗莱吗
Is that Humphrey?
需要少吃点汉堡的那个
The one who needs to lay off the burgers?
中了  真棒
Get it. Go excited.
加油
Come on. Come on.
等等  回去
Wait, wait, go back.
瑞恩
Ryan.
我想要回我的游戏机  谢谢
I'd like my game back, please.
好啊  来拿啊
Fine, take it back.
看  就跟你们说他...
See? Told you guys he was...
谢谢
Thanks.
哥们  那太棒了
Dude. That was awesome.
- 击掌  好样的  - 本杰明·艾萨克·布雷登
- Up high. Nice work. - Benjamin Isaac Braeden.
你是怎么了
What's gotten into you?
他偷了我的游戏机
He stole my game.
你就踢他吗  你什么时候...
So you kick him? Since when is...?
是你叫我儿子打那小子的吗
Did you tell my son to beat up that kid?
怎么了
What?
总得有人教他
I mean, somebody had to teach him
踢霸凌者的蛋蛋
how to kick a bully in the nads.
谁叫你教他任何东西了
Who asked you to teach him anything?
别紧张  我...
Just relax, I...
你怎么还在这里
What are you even still doing here?
我们好久之前一起度过了一个周末罢了
We had one weekend together a million years ago.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
你也无权干涉我儿子
You have no business with my son.
- 莉莎  - 离我们远点
- Lisa. - Just leave us alone.
本
Ben.
谢谢
Thanks.
我在这世上最爱你了  妈妈
I love you most in the whole wide world, Mommy.
我也是  亲爱的
Me too, sweetie.
来  别动
Come on, hold still.
怎么了  妈妈
What's wrong, Mommy?
没事  亲爱的
Nothing, sweetie.
没事
Nothing.
我们现在去吃冰淇淋吗
Are we going for ice cream now?
对
Yep.
我们去吃冰淇淋
We're going for ice cream.
妈妈
Mommy.
我现在能吃冰淇淋了吗
Can I have that ice cream now?
(魔童: 事实还是虚构)
(第二章: 魔童)
(魔童传说)
这镇上的孩子有问题
Something's wrong with the kids in this town.
是啊  可不是嘛
Yeah, tell me about it.
你对魔童有什么了解
So, what do you know about changelings?
邪恶的怪物婴儿吗
Evil monster babies?
不  未必是婴儿
No, not necessarily babies.
那些孩子
The kids.
瘆人的  拿你当午餐盯的孩子
Creepy, stare-at-you-like-you're-lunch kids?
对
Yup.
每个受害人家里都有一个
There's one at every victim's house.
魔童能完美地模仿儿童
So changelings can perfectly mimic children.
据传说  他们会从窗户爬进去  抓走孩子
According to lore, they climb in the window, snatch the kid.
有个孩子家的窗台上有污迹
Now, there were marks on the windowsill at one of the kids house.
我看着像血
Looked to me like blood.
魔童抓走孩子  变成其模样
So changeling grabs the kid, assumes its form...
加入幸福家庭  只为寻乐吗
Joins the happy fam. Just for kicks?
不是的
Not quite.
魔童以母亲为食
Changelings feed on the mom.
吸食滑液
Synovial fluid.
妈妈们的后颈会有奇怪的瘀痕
The moms have these odd bruises on the back of their necks.
魔童能吸食她们几周
Changelings can drain them for a few weeks
妈妈们才会死去
before Mom finally croaks.
然后还有爸爸  保姆
And then there's Dad, the babysitter...
对  所有妨碍了
Yeah. Seems like anyone who gets between
魔童进食的人都会死
a changeling and its food sourse ends up dead.
火是唯一能杀他们的吗
And fire's the only way to waste them?
- 对  - 好啊
- Yep. - Great.
我们只需要冲进去  把孩子拖出来
Now, we'll just bust in, drag the kids out,
在门前草坪上烧死他们
torch them on the front lawn.
邻居们肯定高兴呢
That'll play great with the neighbors.
真孩子呢  他们会怎么样
What about the real ones? What happens to them?
据传说  他们会被藏在地下某处
According to lore, they stash them underground somewhere.
我不知道为什么  但如果是这样
Now, I don't know why, but if it's true,
真孩子可能还在
real kids might be out there somewhere.
那得开始找了
Better start looking.
话说
So
这一带的孩子都可能受害吗
any kid in the neighborhood's vulnerable?
对
Yup.
我们得先去个地方
We gotta make a stop.
我想去看个人
I wanna check on someone.
迪恩  如果真孩子还活着
Dean, if the real kids are still alive,
- 我们没时间...  - 我们必须去
- we don't have time to... - We have to.
- 迪恩  你怎么...  - 我在想
- Dean, what are you...? - I was thinking...
本的生日  我都没拿礼物来
Ben's birthday, I didn't even bring him a present.
没事的
That's okay.
不不  我觉得过意不去  所以
No, no. No, I feel terrible. So
给
here.
休个长周末吧  就你们俩
Take a long weekend. Just the two of you.
- 我请  - 什么
- On me. - What?
是的  我还听说六旗游乐园现在特棒
Yeah. In fact, I hear Six Flags is great this time of year.
现在去吧  不会堵车
Go now, avoid the traffic.
齐格弗里德·胡迪尼  这是谁的卡
Siegfried Houdini. Whose card is this?
我的
Mine.
别管了  能用的  我保证
Never mind. It'll work, I promise.
你走吧
You should leave.
莉莎
Lisa.
妈妈  怎么了
Mommy? What's wrong?
没事  本  没事的
Nothing, Ben, it's cool.
让他走  妈妈
Make him go away, Mommy.
你听到了
You heard him.
走吧
Get out.
莉莎
Lisa.
- 这恐怕不是个好主意  - 快走
- I don't think it's a good idea. - Get out!
他们抓了本  他变了
They took Ben. He's changed.
什么  你确定吗
What? Are you sure?
嗯  我确定  我看过他的窗台了
Yeah. I'm sure. I checked his windowsill.
血吗
Blood?
我觉得不是血
I don't think it is blood.
而且我可能知道孩子们在哪了
And I think I know where the kids are.
(待售)
红土
Red dirt.
窗台上是这个
That's what was on the window.
好  你走前门  我绕到后面
All right. You take the front. I'll go around.
本  本
Ben? Ben.
没事的  我会救你出去  好吗
It's okay. I'm gonna get you out of here, okay?
你在干什么
What do you think you're doing?
这是私产  我要报警了
This is private property. I'm calling the police.
- 你听到了  出去  - 好吧
- You heard me. Get out! - Okay.
等我拿包的  我这就走
Just let me get my bag. I'm going.
我没想惹麻烦
I don't mean to cause any trouble.
妈妈
Mommy?
- 本  - 跟我玩
- Ben. - Play with me.
这可不好玩了  我都哄你上床三次了
This isn't funny anymore. I put you to bed three times already.
但我不想上床
But I don't wanna go to bed.
你真可爱  亲爱的
That's sweet, hon.
来
Come on.
好了  来
All right. Come on.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
小披萨行吗
Mini pizzas okay?
我们只有什锦的了
Deluxe is all we've got.
好啊
Okay.
有意思  还以为你这个月不吃橄榄呢
That's funny. I thought we were anti-olives this month.
没事的
It's okay.
你会逃出去的
You're gonna get out of here, all right?
快点
Hurry!
来  姑娘们  来
Come on, girls. Come on.
来
Come on.
很好  快走
That's it, that's it, keep moving, keep moving.
好了  大家退后
All right. Everybody back. Everybody back.
遮上眼睛
Cover your eyes!
给
Here.
用这个
Use this.
好
All right.
好  本  来
All right. Ben, come on. Come on.
他先来
Him first.
迪恩  还有个妈妈
Dean! Dean, there's a mother.
- 妈妈魔童吗  - 对
- Mother changeling? - Yeah.
我们得快把孩子救出去
We gotta get these kids out. Quick.
那里  还有一个
Right there. Right there. There's one more.
你把锁打掉
You gotta break the lock.
这大概就是魔童没杀孩子们的原因
I guess that's why changeling's keeping the kids alive...
好让魔童妈妈吃他们
so the Mom can snack on them.
来  我扶你
Come on. I got you.
怎么了  妈妈
What's wrong, Mommy?
你不是我儿子
You're not my son.
我就是
Yes, I am.
本呢
Where's Ben?
我就是本
I'm Ben.
我爱你  妈妈
I love you, Mommy.
他们不希望你离开我  妈妈
They don't want you to leave me, Mommy.
妈妈
Mommy?
Mommy.
让我进去
Let me in!
你在干什么  让我进去
What are you doing? Let me in!
让我进去
Let me in, let me in, let me in!
本  快带他们离开
Ben, get them out of here!
妈妈
Mommy!
本
Ben?
Ben!
宝贝  你没事吧
Baby, are you okay?
我没事  妈妈
I'm okay, Mom.
天啊
My God.
到底发生了什么
What the hell just happened?
如果你想的话  我可以解释一切
I'll explain everything if you want me to...
但相信我  你可能不想知道
but trust me, you probably don't.
重要的是本安全了
Important thing is that Ben's safe.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们慢慢来吧
I'm gonna give you guys some time.
来吧
Come on.
魔童
Changelings?
我不是从未提过我是做什么的吗
You know how I never mentioned my job?
我就是做这个的
This is my job.
我还真是不想知道
I so didn't wanna know that.
你觉得他会没事吗
Do you think he'll be okay?
嗯  他会没事的
Yeah, I think he'll be fine.
说真的
Okay, seriously.
你百分百确定他不是我的吗
I mean, you're 100 percent sure that he is not mine? Right?
跟你无关啦
You're off the hook.
他还小时我做过一次血检
I did a blood test when he was a baby.
有个男人
There was this guy. Some
一个机车党酒吧的吧台助理
barback in a biker joint.
怎么了
What?
我有喜欢的型
I had a type.
皮夹克  几道疤
Leather jacket, couple of scars,
没有转寄地址  我都记得呢
no mailing address, I was there.
我当时是挺野的
Guess I was a little wild back then.
那是我当上妈妈之前了
Before I became a mom.
是啊
So yeah.
你放松吧
You can relax.
很好
Good.
你...
You... I...
我怎么觉得你似乎很失望
I swear you look disappointed.
我不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
很奇怪  你的生活
It's weird, you know. Your life,
这房子  这孩子
I mean, this house, the kid.
这不是我的生活  永远不会是
It's not my life, never will be.
我近来出了点事
Some stuff happened to me recently and...
反正  我这种情况的人
Anyway, a guy in my situation,
会开始想
you start to think, you know.
我有天总会死
I'm gonna be gone one day...
除了一辆车  我还能留下什么
and what am I leaving behind besides a car?
我不知道
I don't know.
本或许不是你的孩子
Ben may not be your kid but...
但如果不是你  他就死了
he wouldn't be alive if it wasn't for you.
要我说  这很重大
That's a lot, if you ask me.
我要说一句
You know, just for the record...
你的孩子很棒
you got a great kid.
如果我是他爸我会很骄傲的
I would have been proud to be his dad.
如果
Look if...
如果你想多留一阵
if you wanna stick around for a while...
你可以留下
you're welcome to stay.
我不能
I can't.
我还有很多工作
I got a lot of work to do.
这也不是我的生活
And it's not my life.
(西塞罗松林汽车旅馆  有空房)
我想核实些信息
I needed to check some facts...
跟你的秘书核实一起火灾
with your... with your secretary about a fire
发生在2006年11月24日
that occurred on November 24th, 2006...
位于堪萨斯州劳伦斯
in Lawrence, Kansas.
他叫哈戴克  好  好的
Hardecker was his name. Okay. Great.
我想查他的死亡日期
I was just trying to find out the date he died.
我是菲尔·琼斯警察局长
This is Police Chief Phil Jones.
7月13日
July 13th.
你可以为我查一个
Can you check the records for me
罗伯特·坎贝尔吗  2001年7月19日
for a Robert Campbell, July 19th, 2001.
当场死亡
Dead on arrival.
我想知道死因
What I'm after is, is cause of death.
心脏病吗
Heart condition?
他不是心脏外科手术医生吗
Wasn't he a cardiac surgeon?
难道他不会发现自己有问题吗
Wouldn't he have known about that?
我想查下华莱士太太的死亡信息
I'm looking for information on Mrs. Wallace's death.
两起死亡
Two deaths.
另一个是谁
Who was the other?
爱德·坎贝尔
Ed Campbell?
有人生还吗
Any survivors?
不  我就需要这些  非常感谢
No, that's all I needed, thank you very much.
天啊
My God.
他们死了
They're dead.
都死了
All of them.
我妈妈所有的朋友
All of my mom's friends,
医生  叔叔
her doctor, her uncle.
每一个认识她的人
Everyone who ever knew her
都被系统性地一个个地干掉了
systematically wiped off the map one at a time.
有人费尽力气
Someone went through a hell of a lot of trouble
想掩盖行踪
trying to cover their tracks.
对
Yup.
黄眼恶魔
Yellow-Eyed Demon.
你是怎么回事
So, what's your deal?
你对我如影随形  对我了若指掌
You show up wherever I am, you know all about me,
对我妈了若指掌
you know all about my mom.
我说了  我...
I already told you, I'm just...
对哦  你只是个猎人
Right. Right. Yeah, yeah. Just... Just a hunter.
只是个猎人
Just some hunter
偏巧对我的家庭比我还了解
who happens to know more about my own family than I do.
告诉我你是谁
Just tell me who you are.
萨姆
Sam, it...
就...
Just...
告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you are.
- 那不重要  - 告诉我你是谁
- It doesn't matter. - Just tell me who you are!
好吧
Fine.
别急着动用圣水
Think twice before going for that holy water.
给我个不用的理由
Just give me one reason I shouldn't.
我是来帮你的  萨姆
I'm here to help you, Sam.
这是开玩笑吗
Is that some kind of joke?
上帝可鉴
God's honest truth.
随便吧
Or whatever.
你是个恶魔
You're a demon.
别那么种族歧视
Don't be such a racist.
我来找你是因为我想帮你
I'm here because I wanna help you.
如果你信任我  我就能帮你
And I can if you trust me.
信任你
Trust you?
萨姆  冷静
Sam, calm down.
说  那些凶案
Start talking. All those murders,
恶魔想掩盖什么
what was the demon trying to cover up?
我不知道
I don't know.
我妈妈到底是怎么回事
What happened to my mother?
我真的不知道
I honestly don't know.
我也在查那个
That's what I'm trying to find out.
我只知道这都是为了你
All I know is that it's about you.
什么
What?
你还不懂吗  萨姆
Don't you get it, Sam?
都是为了你
It's all about you.
你妈妈的事  她朋友们的事
What happened to your mom, what happened to her friends.
他们想掩盖他对你做的事
They're trying to cover up what he did to you.
我想帮你查清楚
And I wanna help you figure it out.
你为什么想帮我
Why would you wanna help me?
我自有原因
I have my reasons.
恶魔不都是一样的  萨姆
Not all demons are the same, Sam.
我们的目标也不都一致
Not all of us want the same thing.
我呢
Me?
我想时不时帮帮你
I wanna help you from time to time.
仅此而已
That's all.
如果你让我帮你
And if you let me...
我还有好处给你
there's something in it for you.
你能给我...
What could you possibly...?
我能帮你救你哥哥
I could help you save your brother.